{
  "flashcards": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "mode": "symbol_to_name",
      "front": "ሀ",
      "back": "Ha"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "mode": "syllable_sound",
      "front": "ሀ",
      "back": "hä"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "mode": "syllable_sound",
      "front": "ሀ",
      "back": "hu"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "mode": "syllable_sound",
      "front": "ሀ",
      "back": "hi"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "mode": "syllable_sound",
      "front": "ሀ",
      "back": "ha"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "mode": "syllable_sound",
      "front": "ሀ",
      "back": "he"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "mode": "syllable_sound",
      "front": "ሀ",
      "back": "hə"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "mode": "syllable_sound",
      "front": "ሀ",
      "back": "ho"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "mode": "symbol_to_name",
      "front": "ለ",
      "back": "Le"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "mode": "syllable_sound",
      "front": "ለ",
      "back": "lä"
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "mode": "syllable_sound",
      "front": "ለ",
      "back": "lu"
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "mode": "syllable_sound",
      "front": "ለ",
      "back": "li"
    },
    {
      "id": 13,
      "mode": "syllable_sound",
      "front": "ለ",
      "back": "la"
    },
    {
      "id": 14,
      "mode": "syllable_sound",
      "front": "ለ",
      "back": "le"
    },
    {
      "id": 15,
      "mode": "syllable_sound",
      "front": "ለ",
      "back": "lə"
    },
    {
      "id": 16,
      "mode": "syllable_sound",
      "front": "ለ",
      "back": "lo"
    },
    {
      "id": 17,
      "mode": "symbol_to_name",
      "front": "መ",
      "back": "Me"
    },
    {
      "id": 18,
      "mode": "syllable_sound",
      "front": "መ",
      "back": "mä"
    },
    {
      "id": 19,
      "mode": "syllable_sound",
      "front": "መ",
      "back": "mu"
    },
    {
      "id": 20,
      "mode": "syllable_sound",
      "front": "መ",
      "back": "mi"
    },
    {
      "id": 21,
      "mode": "syllable_sound",
      "front": "መ",
      "back": "ma"
    },
    {
      "id": 22,
      "mode": "syllable_sound",
      "front": "መ",
      "back": "me"
    },
    {
      "id": 23,
      "mode": "syllable_sound",
      "front": "መ",
      "back": "mə"
    },
    {
      "id": 24,
      "mode": "syllable_sound",
      "front": "መ",
      "back": "mo"
    },
    {
      "id": 25,
      "mode": "symbol_to_name",
      "front": "ሰ",
      "back": "Se"
    },
    {
      "id": 26,
      "mode": "syllable_sound",
      "front": "ሰ",
      "back": "sä"
    },
    {
      "id": 27,
      "mode": "syllable_sound",
      "front": "ሰ",
      "back": "su"
    },
    {
      "id": 28,
      "mode": "syllable_sound",
      "front": "ሰ",
      "back": "si"
    },
    {
      "id": 29,
      "mode": "syllable_sound",
      "front": "ሰ",
      "back": "sa"
    },
    {
      "id": 30,
      "mode": "syllable_sound",
      "front": "ሰ",
      "back": "se"
    },
    {
      "id": 31,
      "mode": "syllable_sound",
      "front": "ሰ",
      "back": "sə"
    },
    {
      "id": 32,
      "mode": "syllable_sound",
      "front": "ሰ",
      "back": "so"
    },
    {
      "id": 33,
      "mode": "symbol_to_name",
      "front": "ሸ",
      "back": "She"
    },
    {
      "id": 34,
      "mode": "syllable_sound",
      "front": "ሸ",
      "back": "šä"
    },
    {
      "id": 35,
      "mode": "syllable_sound",
      "front": "ሸ",
      "back": "šu"
    },
    {
      "id": 36,
      "mode": "syllable_sound",
      "front": "ሸ",
      "back": "ši"
    },
    {
      "id": 37,
      "mode": "syllable_sound",
      "front": "ሸ",
      "back": "ša"
    },
    {
      "id": 38,
      "mode": "syllable_sound",
      "front": "ሸ",
      "back": "še"
    },
    {
      "id": 39,
      "mode": "syllable_sound",
      "front": "ሸ",
      "back": "šə"
    },
    {
      "id": 40,
      "mode": "syllable_sound",
      "front": "ሸ",
      "back": "šo"
    },
    {
      "id": 41,
      "mode": "symbol_to_name",
      "front": "ቀ",
      "back": "Qe"
    },
    {
      "id": 42,
      "mode": "syllable_sound",
      "front": "ቀ",
      "back": "qä"
    },
    {
      "id": 43,
      "mode": "syllable_sound",
      "front": "ቀ",
      "back": "qu"
    },
    {
      "id": 44,
      "mode": "syllable_sound",
      "front": "ቀ",
      "back": "qi"
    },
    {
      "id": 45,
      "mode": "syllable_sound",
      "front": "ቀ",
      "back": "qa"
    },
    {
      "id": 46,
      "mode": "syllable_sound",
      "front": "ቀ",
      "back": "qe"
    },
    {
      "id": 47,
      "mode": "syllable_sound",
      "front": "ቀ",
      "back": "qə"
    },
    {
      "id": 48,
      "mode": "syllable_sound",
      "front": "ቀ",
      "back": "qo"
    },
    {
      "id": 49,
      "mode": "symbol_to_name",
      "front": "ተ",
      "back": "Te"
    },
    {
      "id": 50,
      "mode": "syllable_sound",
      "front": "ተ",
      "back": "tä"
    },
    {
      "id": 51,
      "mode": "syllable_sound",
      "front": "ተ",
      "back": "tu"
    },
    {
      "id": 52,
      "mode": "syllable_sound",
      "front": "ተ",
      "back": "ti"
    },
    {
      "id": 53,
      "mode": "syllable_sound",
      "front": "ተ",
      "back": "ta"
    },
    {
      "id": 54,
      "mode": "syllable_sound",
      "front": "ተ",
      "back": "te"
    },
    {
      "id": 55,
      "mode": "syllable_sound",
      "front": "ተ",
      "back": "tə"
    },
    {
      "id": 56,
      "mode": "syllable_sound",
      "front": "ተ",
      "back": "to"
    },
    {
      "id": 57,
      "mode": "symbol_to_name",
      "front": "በ",
      "back": "Be"
    },
    {
      "id": 58,
      "mode": "syllable_sound",
      "front": "በ",
      "back": "bä"
    },
    {
      "id": 59,
      "mode": "syllable_sound",
      "front": "በ",
      "back": "bu"
    },
    {
      "id": 60,
      "mode": "syllable_sound",
      "front": "በ",
      "back": "bi"
    },
    {
      "id": 61,
      "mode": "syllable_sound",
      "front": "በ",
      "back": "ba"
    },
    {
      "id": 62,
      "mode": "syllable_sound",
      "front": "በ",
      "back": "be"
    },
    {
      "id": 63,
      "mode": "syllable_sound",
      "front": "በ",
      "back": "bə"
    },
    {
      "id": 64,
      "mode": "syllable_sound",
      "front": "በ",
      "back": "bo"
    },
    {
      "id": 65,
      "mode": "symbol_to_name",
      "front": "ነ",
      "back": "Ne"
    },
    {
      "id": 66,
      "mode": "syllable_sound",
      "front": "ነ",
      "back": "nä"
    },
    {
      "id": 67,
      "mode": "syllable_sound",
      "front": "ነ",
      "back": "nu"
    },
    {
      "id": 68,
      "mode": "syllable_sound",
      "front": "ነ",
      "back": "ni"
    },
    {
      "id": 69,
      "mode": "syllable_sound",
      "front": "ነ",
      "back": "na"
    },
    {
      "id": 70,
      "mode": "syllable_sound",
      "front": "ነ",
      "back": "ne"
    },
    {
      "id": 71,
      "mode": "syllable_sound",
      "front": "ነ",
      "back": "nə"
    },
    {
      "id": 72,
      "mode": "syllable_sound",
      "front": "ነ",
      "back": "no"
    },
    {
      "id": 73,
      "mode": "symbol_to_name",
      "front": "የ",
      "back": "Ye"
    },
    {
      "id": 74,
      "mode": "syllable_sound",
      "front": "የ",
      "back": "yä"
    },
    {
      "id": 75,
      "mode": "syllable_sound",
      "front": "የ",
      "back": "yu"
    },
    {
      "id": 76,
      "mode": "syllable_sound",
      "front": "የ",
      "back": "yi"
    },
    {
      "id": 77,
      "mode": "syllable_sound",
      "front": "የ",
      "back": "ya"
    },
    {
      "id": 78,
      "mode": "syllable_sound",
      "front": "የ",
      "back": "ye"
    },
    {
      "id": 79,
      "mode": "syllable_sound",
      "front": "የ",
      "back": "yə"
    },
    {
      "id": 80,
      "mode": "syllable_sound",
      "front": "የ",
      "back": "yo"
    }
  ]
}